http://www.intsocdermatol.org/isd-privacy-policy/

© yo- – Fotolia.com
One good thing about some dermatological societies is that they see to it that their members are protected and provide assistance by crafting a privacy policy.
This is beneficial so that the users will know how their personal information will be treated and in order to prevent from being removed, the members are tasked to read the said privacy policy.
A regular update of the privacy policy was made in order to ensure its continuous use and benefits.
For those users who are concerned on how the information they provide is being used, they can check the society’s privacy policy section.
So, what kind of information does dermatological society collect?
The exchange of services on the site will require details such as personal information which needs to be filled out by the user. This information can be the user’s name, credit card details, and social security number and other pertinent data. Some users may be reluctant to provide the said information and might not find it appropriate. Because of this the some has come up with a privacy policy to ensure that this valuable information will not be sold to a third party.
Users can choose from the available options such as receiving email post or telephone contact coming from the web page which is being managed by the internal administration of the page.
The information collected from visitors will not be used for other purposes except for the needs of the page. The ideas collected will be used to make sure that the website is improved and to upgrade the structure and content.
There are also those who use certain type of cookies to store and track information that can be adjusted. If you do not like the page to store data then you have the option of changing your browser but once this is done there are certain areas on the website that cannot be used or will not be accessible.
There are instances where in the company will make use of advertisements so that services can be provided for free for visitors and members.
The administrators will provide news and services if there are any changes on the websites. Clients will also be updated regarding publications that matter to them or they can request this from the administration email.
Recent Posts
Taking Care of Your Hair
Locking in Skins Moisture
Addressing Acne Vulgaris
ISID Privacy Policy
ISID Journal
ISID Terms and Conditions
ISID Access Agreement
What is ISID?
Categories
Services
Uncategorized
© copyright by intsocdermatol
